The first quarter results of this IS A Lumba man zone have
come, there has been an increase of more than
130 percent in the company's profit on yearly basis
and there has been an
increase of about 30 percent in computer insurance hospital premium also.
Let's talk about the results
from the management of the company and first of all we would
like to know from you how the company is working,
if we look at the profit of the company, then a
growth of 335 percent has been registered, the
performance of the health insurance has been very
good, while in both retail and corporate,
we have seen a growth of about 3434 percent,
I can explain a little trend,
what are you doing that is
improving the performance and what are these hotels for the future,
if you would have seen that
our overall growth in health insurance has been 38 percent
and such numbers, if you
look at the growth of the industry, turmeric and health, in this quarter, the
growth has been about 20 percent, not
physical, you will see rebellion, so subscribe to them,
if you subscribe, then
subscribe and
subscribe
and
if you have seen those who are fine and
talk about butter positive Britain, then there  But
here
we have Office
Ideal, if you have seen it, please
subscribe
and
subscribe to the Channel. Please
subscribe and
subscribe to it. Now, the
justification
from this is a traditional look at how we can take
care of preventive balance. We are
focusing a lot on that and take care of
preventive. We have been
investing in order to
take
care of every river water customer for the last 2 years.
Gopal ji, hello, I am saying, please
subscribe and it was created in a good way.
You feel that the online platform is going to be
there and
tell me how the
related questions will be answered
more fundamentally. We will talk about this number,
subscribe to this number setting,
subscribe to the products and if we talk about different
levels, then to
talk about it also, it is necessary to subscribe to
it,
subscribe to the
edition
appointed
board,
subscribe to for rice, this notification,
CT
Gautam
and subscribe
cheating and settled in the last nine to ten
inch ad speech at the end of 130  Almost
lost your deed, the help agency manager
definitely the number which is in the market, the
number of
subscribers is increased, secondly if you subscribe by clicking on subscribe,
secondly
if we talk then
subscribe,
if we look at your corporate quartz insurance
act, then there has been a good growth in it,
it is participating in your overall business in a very good way,
what is the future trend regarding this
and also tell us about the product mix,
in the coming time, will we see
more focus of the company on health and motor insurance,
a
certificate with questions first and the first
question was Kapishrestha above, if you must have seen the
problems with your contribution to the
great premium and single digit is
Switzerland 24th properly and two to three
percent contribution has been
towards professionals, all are aware and Kailash Pathak Pro
features which you have just written about or Android
preparations, from this the
result of the integration tweet
in Indian side it is noble and support the schemes'
controversy is that sensitive you
can ask any question, this paint heart  Commitment
for three years kid and Indian farmer has
some prominence in underwriting team which
support authentication father I will sew it this
nothing but commitment so it will cause some inconvenience to
Twitter followers of commitment by turning on this setting this
basically layer market will be
seen this page setup appointed
ground with respect to the terms of this
scheme disclosures were given cement questions have
increased significantly there also they also have
not operated research arrangement so there we
see whether there is any change in the cost on the budget and screens or
not let's
also see that till the
reverse of plane servicing and raw search
tiffin changes are happening in these three areas for
example in the terms for this cream stomach
cancer state saver mode on *
80 scheme judge this means this meeting this
report chapter
maximum loss the missions company took part in the
event of schedule set that when
you
ji Gopal ji let's go so we have talked about the results
and the good future of the last quarter  Let's
talk about this, there are some reports in
which it is being said that it is a matter of a few days
when on the policies of life insurance companies,
tell us that if this happens then
how will the corporation stand for you or for the companies of June 19
and how will you
deal with it, so
as I told you that there is a segment
where there was a lot of impression level plug
anniversary this bundle and last couple of years,
if you see as of today, the first
travel insurance of it is very low
that soon single digit number you are thinking
children that if you increase the rest of the
added to print were significant from Saturday
interpreted marked into alleged increased
number of people will have health insurance
cover friends, if you look at the opposition in the market,
it has increased significantly inside its
proof for electrification passport, secondly as
I said that whatever is there as of today, it has
fired this prominent leader
factor hospitalization insurance but if you
see as of today, Monday
is health care friends, last quarter health
care friends almost  Authors of the
Pacific
Judo which was not being celebrated in any
form to any form of the inch recent
activities for players in the market
with sister in law a little this number date
Arvind Singh Dev Tyagi and take care
and here we have discussed a lot of acid traffic
signals WhatsApp collection president
scenario where you want to stay in the
students and staff product options which will
come to the market will also give room for
playlist ok okay
thank you Gopal ji
with this we conclude the interview but thank you very much for
joining us
and for discussing the future outlook of the company of Clans
big news if we
look at the stock price then
even after the beginning the stock of Salon Watt is
performing very well and
whoever has upgraded the rating on it has
upgraded the underperform rating from outperform to outperform
and they have given a target of 1470